[Fate Chooses You]
[Episode 28]
Kneel!
Master,
we split up into 2 teams
to pursue those human pills.
With the 2 Guardians presiding over it,
all disciples of the Sun Moon Cavern
have been captured.
Several disciples from Lingji Mountain
and Tianyuan Sect
are still on the run.
We've sent someone
to continue the pursuit.
This is
the Young Sect Master of Lingji Mountain.
He killed Wenyin.
Lin An's son,
at the Foundation Establishment?
You know my father's name, yet you
still dare to tie me up.
Aren't you afraid my father will come
and level your Qinghong Sect
to the ground?
Look at yourselves,
you bunch of monsters.
How dare you call yourselves
the Phoenix Gods of North Xiang?
If you have the guts,
go to the Central Plains.
You are even worse
than wild chickens!
How dare you!
Xu Feng...
Xu Feng, wake up!
Xu Feng!
While he's still breathing,
we can extract his immortal perception,
so it won't go to waste.
What are you doing?
Where are you taking him?
Fu Tian, you bastard!
I swear I will kill you!
Xu Feng!
I'm going to kill you today!
-I'll kill you!
-Take him away.
Go.
We need to quickly catch and bring back
those from Lingji Mountain.
We can't let them escape the desert.
Otherwise, we won't have enough people
or enough quantity.
The aptitude of these human pills
is quite good.
There are even
a few Nascent Soul cultivators among them.
Especially the male cultivator
who escaped from the paper mill
a few days ago.
We kept him here
in order to translate
the War Demons' books.
And the books
have already been sent back
to the Central Plains.
I bet the Overlord
will be very satisfied.
Given what you're saying, Master,
do you plan
to let that male cultivator go?
You need to say no more.
The Master has his own judgment.
His own judgment?
I'm afraid
he is just holding onto old ties
and being irresolute.
How dare you!
Lord Baori,
this is North Xiang,
the territory of our Qinghong Sect.
As long as you stay here,
you are just a member
of the Qinghong Sect.
You must know your place.
Vajra Xunmu.
Do you have any instructions, Lord Tiling?
Who rescued
Lu Qianqiao that day?
How would I know?
You don't know?
You are in charge
of the paper mill's security.
An outsider casually
sneaked in
and rescued him.
You don't know?
About this matter,
I have already pleaded guilty
to the Cult Leader.
I messed up.
But as for who that person was
and how they got in,
I have no idea at all.
After all, I'm just a lowly cultivator
at Foundation Establishment.
Lord Tiling,
you're a superior cultivator
at the Void Stage.
Wouldn't it be a piece of cake
for you to bring them back?
[Yunmo Inn]
Are you all right?
How about you?
You were also injured just now.
I'm fine.
Who are the people
chasing us just now?
Are they from the Wushuang Society?
The Wushuang Society
doesn't have that many cultivators.
I'm afraid they're the forces
from North Xiang.
Even a mighty dragon
cannot suppress the local snake.
We must leave as soon as possible.
Don't worry, Junior.
With you here with me,
I'm not worried.
The Master told us to catch
those from the Wushuang Society.
I thought they were just a few mortals,
and it would be an easy catch.
I didn't expect it
to be this much trouble.
Things are unpredictable.
It's all those demonic cultivators' fault.
Were it not for them,
we wouldn't have come here,
nor ended up in such trouble.
Demonic cultivators...
Are they really demonic cultivators?
Senior Bai?
I ran into some heretical cultivators
practicing demonic techniques before.
Relying on their superior powers,
they killed the innocent at will
and treated human lives like nothing.
Their eyes were like those of beasts,
with no trace of joy or sorrow,
only filled with cruelty and greed.
Just one look at them was enough
to tell that they had become demonic.
But those from the Wushuang Society
are different.
How are they different?
Their eyes are very clear.
Most of them are ordinary people,
too weak to even defend themselves.
But they are very courageous.
They seem very certain,
not having even the slightest doubt
in what they believe.
But what do they believe in?
They believe they are right.
They believe their deaths
are valuable.
What exactly are you trying to say?
I don't know either.
I'm just a little confused.
Senior Bai,
we are both disciples
of the immortal sect
and also Heavenly Talents
born on September 9th.
We still need to save the world
and rescue the people.
We will do whatever
the Sect says.
Why overthink it?
Heavenly Talents.
Do you believe it?
Of course I do.
But
there are too many people in this world
born on September 9th.
Not everyone is necessarily a savior.
But I know
you definitely are.
Why?
It's hard to explain,
but I've thought so since childhood.
Do you still believe
in the Crazy Taoist's prophecy?
He said that among
the Heavenly Talents born
on September 9th,
there will be a savior of the world.
I really used to believe
that person would be you.
Get some rest, Junior.
I'll go check on the other juniors.
Come on, bear with it.
Here you are, have some water.
Are you okay?
Alright.
Gently, gently.
Bear with it.
Here, have some water.
Come on.
Someone's coming.
Senior Bai,
Senior Sima is back.
Open the door.
Yes.
Quickly, come on.
Come on, take it slow.
-Help me.
-Be careful.
Hold him up.
Sit down.
I'll get you some medicine.
What happened?
We were ambushed.
You were ambushed, too?
Apply the medicine now.
Do you know who did it?
No idea.
Where is Lin Muhan?
We got separated.
Go rest up.
Come on, have some water.
Here.
Gently.
Alright, alright.
Senior, it's time for us to leave.
The Sect Master ordered that
once we're done
with the Wushuang Society's matters,
we must return to the sect immediately.
The juniors from Lingji Mountain
all have leg injuries.
I'm afraid they can't travel.
Besides, we don't have enough horses.
How can we leave?
On the brink of disaster,
why care about the lives
of those from Lingji Mountain?
Are you going to abandon them?
Or
do you have a better idea?
It's a matter of life and death, Senior.
Don't be soft-hearted.
Must you drag down
our Tianyuan Sect disciples
to die here?
Do you want it?
All disciples of the immortal sects
are one family.
If we unite as one,
we might be able to leave together.
Bai Zongying,
let me remind you.
Even if you are
the sect's Heavenly Talent,
you must consider the Master's orders
and the disciples of our Tianyuan Sect.
Qinghong Sect.
Here we meet again.
So the ones who ambushed us before
were you.
We have never offended the Qinghong Sect.
You burned
a huge library of ours,
and you call that not offending us?
Before coming to North Xiang,
the elders in our sect
already sent a letter
to your sect master.
Whatever the grievances,
the Tianyuan Sect
has given an explanation.
I don't know about that.
I only know
that today,
none of you will escape.
Senior Bai,
why waste words with this enchantress?
Bitch!
What are you doing?
And what are you doing?
Take her away first.
No, we should leave together.
Go! Hurry!
Senior Bai!
You saved An and the others?
Yes.
You're still alive.
He didn't die either.
He was alive when I left.
Where are you going?
If he's not dead,
my senior sister will be in danger.
You are not completely
heartless.
You've been waiting for me here
just to ask me these questions?
What else could it be?
Are you waiting
for me to apologize?
Isn't it just one word?
Is it that important?
Fine.
♪ Hear the Gu curse
turn into cries for help ♪
Sorry.
Can I leave now?
Why?
♪ Blood-stained hand, sword drawn ♪
What do you mean?
Why did you treat me like this?
♪ Trapped in Qianyan Cave ♪
What did I do to you?
You and I crossed paths by chance,
♪ Even hell must be broken free from ♪
and you did this voluntarily.
I already told you
to stay away from me.
♪ With every stroke of hatred ♪
You didn't listen.
♪ Let it grow into a dagger I wear ♪
Why are you looking at me
with that look?
♪ No need to show me mercy there ♪
Didn't your master say
I am your tribulation?
♪ Let me take every blow ♪
Now you have gotten over
this tribulation.
You should go back now.
♪ Drag my wounds through the hollow road ♪
Go achieve your great Dao.
♪ I'll pluck the passion
locked in my brow ♪
♪ At the end of the mountains,
I pick up fireflies now ♪
What?
♪ Burn me down, I feel no pain ♪
Do you want to take revenge on me?
You've lost an arm now,
♪ I believe Heaven sees all ♪
so you might not be my match.
♪ Its wrath shines upon demons ♪
♪ But who will show me mercy? ♪
Didn't you say
the core of fate never changes?
♪ I believe I'm innocent ♪
♪ Turned into dust and scattered away ♪
Why
didn't you foresee what I've done to you?
You remember what I said.
♪ I accept the blame of
numerous accusations ♪
Why don't you remember my kindness?
♪ I offer no defense ♪
♪ To protect what I believe is worth it ♪
The day I fell to the bottom of the cliff,
♪ I admit my heart
is as hard as iron and stone ♪
I was attacked
by countless poisonous bugs.
♪ Call me cold if you must ♪
I was already exhausted
dealing with them.
♪ I'll risk it all ♪
Then when your fa...
When Xia Xuanzi woke up,
I knew I was no match for him.
Only by using my bracelet did I
♪ Hear the Gu curse
turn into cries for help ♪
barely survive.
I thought you would definitely
come back for me.
♪ Blood-stained hand, sword drawn ♪
I even thought
♪ Trapped in Qianyan Cave ♪
when you came back,
what if I couldn't protect you?
♪ Even hell must be broken free from ♪
I walked out of Qianyan Cave step by step.
♪ With every stroke of hatred ♪
Don't you have anything
♪ Let it grow into a dagger I wear ♪
you want to say to me?
You remember all that stuff.
♪ No need to show me mercy there ♪
But how come you don't remember
♪ Let me take every blow ♪
a single bad thing others do?
Me, going back for you?
Don't forget
how you fell down the cliff.
♪ Drag my wounds through the hollow road ♪
Don't you feel
even a bit happy seeing me?
♪ I'll pluck the passion
locked in my brow ♪
♪ At the end of the mountains,
I pick up fireflies now ♪
♪ Burn me down, I feel no pain ♪
I am the daughter of Xia Xuanzi.
♪ I believe Heaven sees all ♪
Whether I admit it or not,
♪ Its wrath shines upon demons ♪
I am his daughter.
♪ But who will show me mercy? ♪
I am heartless by nature.
The earlier you realize it,
♪ I believe I'm innocent ♪
♪ Turned into dust and scattered away ♪
the better it'll be for you.
If you don't want to die,
just stop following me.
♪ I accept the blame of
numerous accusations ♪
♪ I offer no defense ♪
♪ To protect what I believe is worth it ♪
♪ I admit my heart
is as hard as iron and stone ♪
♪ Call me cold if you must ♪
♪ I'll risk it all ♪
♪ All guilt falls on me ♪
♪ I've owed far too much ♪
♪ Just let my heart rot completely ♪
♪ Just see me as the demon in your eyes ♪
♪ I believe Heaven sees all ♪
♪ Its wrath shines upon demons ♪
♪ But who will show me mercy? ♪
♪ I accept this trial of love
fate has given me ♪
♪ I take in both love and hate alike ♪
Vajra Xunmu.
What's with her?
Vajra Xunmu,
Lord Tiling captured her
on the way back.
The Lord ordered us
to lock her up first.
What are you looking at?
You already end up here,
and you are still so fierce.
Give me a smile,
and I'll give you a gift
that you definitely like.
How's that?
How boring.
Come with me.
Take her with us.
Sheng?
Sheng!
Senior Sister?
Sheng.
Senior!
Why are you here?
See?
I told you there's a gift
you'd definitely like.
What did you do to her?
Are you blind?
Can't you see for yourself?
Senior Sister,
I'm fine.
Let me check on you.
How moving.
Since you're finally reunited,
you must have a lot to catch up on.
I'll leave you to it.
Anyway,
you don't have much time left.
They are having a reunion.
Why are you standing still here?
What?
Do you want me to find you
a paramour in prison?
I saw you looking so jealous,
so I wanted to comfort you.
Why would I be jealous?
When the living meet the living,
it's called a reunion.
When the living meet the dead,
it's called visiting a grave.
-Does it hurt?
-Look at you.
-No, it doesn't.
-You must have no family.
If you are really envious,
you can go visit a grave.
But make sure you get the right grave.
Don't visit the wrong one.
Even if you are willing to kneel,
they might not want to acknowledge
an unworthy descendant like you.
Too weak.
Come again.
You want to die, huh?
Don't rush. One at a time.
Your turn will come anyway.
Bring the boy from Lingji Mountain over.
Lock him up with this one.
How were you injured by the Qinghong Sect?
I'm fine.
It doesn't hurt anymore.
Then how were you caught
and brought here?
What about Tang You and An?
Are they here too?
I sent them back to the Central Plains.
The "Unparalleled Secret Magic" was
also safely
brought back.
Glad to hear that.
Then why did you come back?
That bastard, Xia Xuanzi, is still alive.
I was worried about you.
Silly Sheng.
You shouldn't have come back.
Thankfully, I came back.
Otherwise, being thousands of miles
away from you,
I wouldn't know if you were safe.
How were you caught, Senior Sister?
Where is Lu Qianqiao?
Why isn't he here?
He left you behind and ran away?
It's a long story.
[Liubo Temple]
When I woke up,
I saw Rust-Sword.
Why did the Qinghong Sect
set up such a huge maze formation?
What are they up to?
To hunt down immortal sect disciples.
Those lunatics from the Qinghong Sect
want the immortal perception
inside the cultivators' bodies.
But they are also cultivators.
Why would they dig out
other people's immortal perception?
Yeah.
Why?
Master.
How is Niankong?
Dharma King Niankong was
hit in the heart meridian by Bai Zongying.
His blood is flowing in reverse.
It doesn't look good.
What a coincidence.
Master,
it just so happens that
there are
cultivators
at Nascent Soul
in this batch of human pills.
We can use them to refine
the golden liquid
to prolong Niankong's life.
The elderly Niankong
has been at the Nascent Soul stage
for nearly a decade.
This time, he was even
severely injured
by a junior who had just reached
the Nascent Soul stage.
How does he have the face
to take this golden liquid?
Niankong is one of our Qinghong Sect.
No matter what he did
or whether he is useful,
we must protect him.
After all,
closeness and distance are
quite easy to distinguish.
How do you distinguish?
Isn't it just a Nascent Soul cultivator?
There is more than one in prison.
I'll go catch one.
Senior Sister,
are you tired?
Would you like to take a nap?
I can't fall asleep.
It's right ahead.
What are you doing?
Take her away.
Don't you dare hurt my senior sister!
Come at me if you have the guts!
Don't touch them!
Bullying two girls
doesn't make you any tougher!
Sheng!
Don't touch my senior sister!
Sheng.
No.
Don't.
Take me away with you.
Take me!
Do you really want to die?
Don't hurt her.
I'll go with you.
As you wish.
Why waste time?
The Master is still waiting.
Hurry up.
No.
Senior Sister,
don't go with them.
No!
Don't worry.
I'll be fine.
Take her away.
No.
Senior Sister.
Go!
Senior Sister!
Let her go!
-Let her go!
-Senior Sister!
Let her go!
Senior Sister...
[Liubo Temple]
[Tomb of Duan Xianyin, my dear master]
What is this?
How could Master die?
[Erected by Disciple Lu Qianqiao]
Why is my name on it?
I set up this tombstone?
If I set it up,
how come I don't remember it?
Lu,
I...
Sachets, pouches, and small pendants!
Come and take a look!
Small pendants!
[Duan Xianyin from Liubo Temple]
Come in.
The War Demon's physique is
truly mysterious.
You feel no pain,
and your wounds heal quickly.
Qianqiao,
how about we try again and see
to what extent
your wounds can heal?
Time to eat.
I don't like it.
You have to eat even if you don't like it.
She'll come beat you again soon.
You won't survive if you don't eat.
If you die,
I'll die, too.
Why?
She bought me to serve you.
If you die,
she will beat me to death, too.
Lu,
do you think
we can grow up safely?
My family is dirt-poor.
My father was in debt,
so he sold me.
He said that when I grow up,
I can escape from the master's place
and run back to find him.
Lu,
do you think I can grow up safely?
I don't know.
Even if I grow up,
I won't go look for him.
Lu,
we have to survive.
let's survive together.
Master,
it's time to take your medicine.
You did it...
Don't come over.
Don't come any closer.
Don't come any closer!
Lu! Hurry!
Lu,
you've recalled everything?
Yes,
I've recalled everything.
I was nothing but a piece of wood.
You gave me the power
to awaken my consciousness,
so I could perceive everything
in this world.
Back then, you were troubled by the past
and had trouble falling asleep.
I used spells
to help you.
My power comes from you.
When you are strong, I am strong.
When you are weak, I am weak.
But unfortunately,
now that you are injured,
my power can't hold on,
and the memory is unlocked.
Lu,
I've never figured out
why you sealed
this part of your memory.
Duan Xianyin maltreated you.
She was a heretical cultivator.
She took you as her disciple
just in order to use you
to get the body-tempering technique
of the War Demons.
Someone like her
deserved to die.
Why feel guilty?
It's not about guilt.
Then why?
Because I don't want to lie anymore.
Humans always like to ask some questions.
Where are you from?
Where do you live?
These were what I was asked
most of the time back then.
But where am I from?
And where is my home?
I am a half-blood
of War Demons and humans.
My father was a spy for the Human Race,
hell-bent on wiping out the War Demons.
My mother hated my father's betrayal
and wanted to kill me, too.
Caught in the middle,
which side am I on?
A person living in this world,
with no roots,
no home,
is like
a lost soul.
So you sealed away
that memory,
lying to yourself
that you came from Liubo Temple
in North Xiang
and had a master who treated you well.
So stupid.
Yes, so stupid.
Senior,
Randeng is back.
Greetings, Sect Master.
Why are you back alone?
While pursuing the Wushuang Society,
I was ambushed by the Qinghong Sect
and got separated from the others.
Where is Bai?
Senior Bai
insisted on protecting
the disciples of Lingji Mountain.
I tried to persuade him,
but he refused to leave.
Later,
the people from the Qinghong Sect
caught up.
He asked me to take Jiang Ji
and leave first.
As for what happened to him later,
I don't know.
If Bai falls into
the hands of the Qinghong Sect,
I'm afraid things won't end well.
Should we send someone to look for him?
Randeng, when did you and Bai
split up?
At least 10 days ago.
It's too late.
Miss Xin,
you're finally awake.
I heard that in just a few months,
your cultivation level rose
from the Qi Refining stage to Nascent Soul.
How did you do it?
You're from an immortal sect,
yet why are you mixed up with the people
from the Wushuang Society?
Which side are you really on?
And which side are you on?
You are the master of the Sihe Library,
yet you sat by and watched
the people from immortal sects
burn all the books.
Since you are a cultivator,
why are you secretly hunting down
those from the immortal sects?
In the name of the Qinghong Sect,
you lurk in the dark
doing despicable things.
Who on earth are you? A human or a ghost?
You're sharp-tongued.
No wonder Lu Qianqiao likes you.
Who on earth are you?
Me?
I am a devil
who crawled out of hell,
the knife that helps people cut out
rotten flesh,
your restless inner desires,
and above all,
endless destruction.
I am
the king of all living beings,
the Nirvana Divine Phoenix!
You really know how to flatter yourself.
How dare you!
Master, don't waste your breath on her.
Let's just dig out her immortal perception
and throw her out to feed the dogs!
How stubborn you are.
What a waste
of such an excellent immortal perception.
Please hold on, Master.
This woman has close ties
with Lu Qianqiao.
Keeping her alive
might help us lure
Lu Qianqiao here.
Yingying,
we're only taking her immortal perception,
not her life.
We'll just feed her several bowls of tonic
and spare her life.
And we can still lure him into our trap.
What's going on?